export const lvl5 = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: `What popular Australian dessert is often served in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Pavlova', 'B) Cheesecake', 'C) Tiramisu'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Pavlova',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: `What type of steak is a local delicacy?`,
    answers: ['A) Venison steak', 'B) Lamb steak', 'C) Chicken steak'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Lamb steak',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: `What is a popular beverage in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Coffee', 'B) Smoothies', 'C) Soda'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Coffee',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: `Which type of cuisine is particularly popular in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) Asian cuisine', 'B) Italian cuisine', 'C) French cuisine'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Asian cuisine',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: `What local dish is made with kangaroo meat?`,
    answers: ['A) Kangaroo burger', 'B) Kangaroo steak', 'C) Kangaroo pie'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Kangaroo burger',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: `What is a popular food market in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Farmers Market',
      'B) Sydney Fish Market',
      'C) Adelaide Central Market',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Farmers Market',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: `What festival celebrates food and wine in Brisbane?`,
    answers: [
      'A) Brisbane Food Festival',
      'B) Queensland Food Festival',
      'C) Sydney Food Festival',
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'A) Brisbane Food Festival',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: `Which brewery is famous for its craft beers in Brisbane?`,
    answers: ['A) XXXX Brewery', 'B) Tooheys Brewery', 'C) Carlton Brewery'],
    correctAnswer: 'A) XXXX Brewery',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: `What popular brunch spot in Brisbane is known for its organic menu?`,
    answers: ['A) Café Brisbane', 'B) The Vegan Café', 'C) The Breakfast Club'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) The Vegan Café',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: `What type of wine is commonly produced in Queensland?`,
    answers: ['A) Shiraz', 'B) Chardonnay', 'C) Merlot'],
    correctAnswer: 'B) Chardonnay',
  },
];
